const questions = [
  [
    {
      question: 'What is a hackathon?',
      answer:
        'A hackathon is an event where people collaborate intensively to build a project from scratch in a short amount of time.'
    },
    {
      question: 'Virtual or in-person this year?',
      answer:
        'StormHacks 2022 will be completely online and hosted on a virtual event platform.'
    },
    {
      question: 'Can I work on a previous project?',
      answer:
        'No, all projects must be built from scratch during StormHacks. However, you are welcome to brainstorm project ideas before the event.'
    },
    {
      question: 'What if I’ve never been to a hackathon?',
      answer:
        'StormHacks welcomes students of all skill levels and backgrounds. Whether you’re a newcomer or a hackathon veteran, we’ll have talks, workshops and mentors to help you with your project throughout the event. All you need to bring is your eagerness to learn.'
    },
    {
      question: 'What kind of activities will there be?',
      answer:
        'The hackathon will be packed with activities such as wellness workshops, games, trivia and more all throughout the event! You might even win some prizes by participating in our mini contests.'
    },
    {
      question: 'Is there a theme for StormHacks?',
      answer: 'Yes! We will be revealing the theme(s) closer to the event date.'
    },
    {
      question: 'What platform is the event on?',
      answer: 'We will be hosting the event on Socio.'
    }
  ],
  [
    {
      question: 'How will we receive swag?',
      answer:
        'Swag will be shipped out to the address you provide during registration! Please note that some swag is limited to hackers in Canada who submit a project.'
    },
    {
      question: 'Who can participate?',
      answer:
        'Students of any education level can apply to StormHacks, as long as they are still enrolled when the event takes place in February.'
    },
    {
      question: 'How much does it cost?',
      answer:
        'Admission to StormHacks is completely free for those w are eligible. We will provide all the resources you need to build incredible and impactful projects.'
    },
    {
      question: 'How many people can be on a team?',
      answer:
        'You can form teams of 2-4 people. Don’t worry if you can’t find a team beforehand, event execs will help you find opportunities to connect with others during the event.'
    },
    {
      question: 'How will communication work during the event?',
      answer:
        'All pre-event communications will be via email, so sign up for the StormHacks mailing list! During the event, we’ll be using Socio to announce important information and updates to all attendees.'
    },
    {
      question: 'When do hacker applications open?',
      answer:
        'Hacker applications will open on Monday, December 27th! Stay tuned for more information.'
    },
    {
      question: '404: Questions not found?',
      answer:
        "Contact us at info@stormhacks.com with your question and we'll get back to you as soon as we can!"
    }
  ]
]

export default questions
